MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Grand Prince Cheongheon is
hereby confined to his quarters.
Who goes there?
I have brought you porridge.
Please eat before it gets cold.
It is you.
Have you no fear coming here?
If anyone sees you…
I cannot discern
where falsehood ends and truth begins.
The uncertainty leaves me
helpless with dread.
Please enlighten me.
What is the truth?
How could one be so naive?
This is why you so easily fall prey
to exploitative men.
Pardon?
Do nothing.
Find your path to survive,
just as you did
at the royal interrogation.
This is…
my final command to you.
Kang Dan-sim.
Never…
set foot in this place again.
Who…
are you really?
Dan-sim of the Kang clan.
What did you just…
Who are you?
What sort of question is that?
Have you been day-drinking?
Raving in broad daylight.
A woman keeps appearing in my dreams.
A court lady
with no friends or family.
At first, I thought it was just a dream.
But it's strange.
Because I feel like
that woman might be you.
Have I lost my mind?
At least you know it sounds crazy.
You're mistaking
nonsense dreams for reality.
-A nonsense dream?
-Yes, a nonsense dream.
Showing up dressed like that,
rambling about dreams?
You have most certainly lost your mind.
I shall go on ahead.
Come back when you are decent.
EPISODE 9
THAT'S FIRST LOVE FOR YOU
-How should we proceed?
-Follow him.
Who…
are you really?
A woman keeps appearing in my dreams.
A court lady…
with no friends or family.
A dream?
Mr. Cha, this launch is a huge success.
If I'd known you'd hit
a home run like this,
I would've invested early on.
I couldn't agree more.
At this rate, you could even break
into the US market
and dominate the whole industry.
No need to be intimidated already.
I'll be sure to leave some scraps.
At least you know it sounds crazy.
You're mistaking
nonsense dreams for reality.
-Hello. Hi there.
-Hello.
Can I ask
why you have been trailing me
like a shadow since we arrived?
Well?
You should be working the room.
Do what you can
to land yourself another ad.
Not really my jurisdiction.
Your jurisdiction?
Why would I hawk my face like some peddler
if I have an agency?
What do I pay you for?
You can forget about making easy money.
That brat always has to have
the last word.
-Shin Seo-ri.
-Gosh!
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Are you doing okay?
Don't worry about it.
Just a nonsense dream, remember?
It left me feeling incredibly unsettled.
Choi Mun-do just had to show up too.
He was like a budding tyrant in my dream.
I guess dreams really are
an extension of consciousness.
Maybe it was not just a dream?
Could he really be seeing the past?
Here you are, Se-gye.
Does it just go in one ear
and out the other with you?
I clearly told you to go
through my office until the engagement--
What if someone hears you?
You're right.
I wasn't thinking. I'll be more careful.
You can't be serious, Se-gye.
In public, I'm still your--
Yes, you are his fiancée. That you are.
My ears are about to bleed.
Cha Se-gye, I will allow it.
Go hold hands and take a lap.
Even dying wishes are honored.
She is not asking for much.
Go on. Grant her her last wish.
Who are you to give him permission?
You are seriously so exhausting.
Goodness, you're all already here.
Grandfather, what brings you here?
This is my grandson's brand launch.
Why wouldn't I be here?
Welcome, Grandfather.
If you had told me beforehand,
I would have escorted you.
Tae-hee, are you already playing the wife?
My Se-gye
is so blessed when it comes to women.
He certainly is.
Grandfather, I need
to introduce you to someone.
The official face of Dynaestie
and the key
to our sold-out success. Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
Shin… Shin Seo-ri?
Nice to meet you,
Grandpapa!
What the…
Hey, stop it.
Just stop.
-He's not your grandpapa yet.
-He isn't?
Just call him Chairman.
Right.
You also badgered me to call you
"Mr. Cha" at the beginning.
I guess being sensitive
about titles like a boomer
is a family trait?
She's a funny one.
So, the model treats the CEO
like her buddy now?
No, it's not like that.
It's like…
You see, she's filming
a historical drama right now.
She's very absorbed in her role.
Method acting, you see.
Chairman Jung is here, sir.
-Over there.
-Chairman Jung. Shall we…
-Chairman Jung is here?
-Yes.
Yes, let's go,
Grandfather.
Why, that little…
I was just lucky.
Not luck. That's skill.
-Stating the obvious.
-Unbelievable.
-Good to see you.
-Hello, sir.
-We should get together.
-Sure.
My grandson really hit it big
this time launching Dynaestie.
-He did.
-It must succeed.
Yes, I heard the rumors.
I'm sure he'll do great.
-Well, he's a hard worker, so probably…
-Yes.
With today's launch event,
Mr. Cha's image in the industry
is on the road to recovery.
Response from both the media
and within Chail has been favorable.
It must be the halo effect
from the Chairman.
And the anticipation
building around Chail's successor.
What about that nurse?
Is she still unconscious?
Yes, but her medical team
has been paid off,
so they should reach out
if anything changes.
There must be no mistakes this time.
As a court lady in Mr. Cha's dream?
If he's seeing the past,
it's not a prophetic dream.
Could it be something like reincarnation?
I know you are a seer and all,
but you should still keep up
with the times.
How can you spout such nonsense
in this day and age,
where palanquins fly?
If we can transcend time and space,
why not reincarnation?
If anything, your situation
makes less sense. Seriously.
If it really is reincarnation,
do you have anyone you suspect he is?
You said that a man
named Choi Mun-do was the king.
Then wouldn't Mr. Cha
be someone close to him too?
Your dreams have a storyline?
Have you been under stress lately?
How could I not be?
I'm surrounded by minefields.
Never mind that.
Just prescribe me more sleeping pills.
To knock me out cold.
That's not something
you can suppress just by sheer will.
Just relax and go with the flow.
Who knows? It could be a prophetic dream.
A prophetic dream…
Are you even listening to me?
And you call yourself a doctor.
It's not the future. It's the past.
Who cares if it's the past or future?
It's still all connected to the present.
You shouldn't assume time is linear.
There could be parallel timelines.
Did you join a cult?
I didn't expect the Chairman
to make a personal appearance.
It's safe to see this as a signal, right?
A signal?
Yeah, I guess it's safe
to call it a signal from the brain.
For what feels like an eternity,
I've been waiting
for him to summon us back
to headquarters and finally--
I did wait for an eternity.
It was so bad I even dreamed about it.
Our commute will be a bit longer,
but who cares? We can just sleep less.
Yeah. I haven't been sleeping much lately.
You could call it a symptom
of sleep deprivation.
You know, you can be
so insightful sometimes, Mr. Son.
Yes, sir.
Then, how about a vacation
as a reward before we return…
Sure, go ahead.
Actually, you can take PTO when I do.
Sure. When would that be?
When I'm dead.
What's wrong?
My teeth have been a bit sensitive lately.
My gums are throbbing.
Even if you skip taking PTO,
you shouldn't skip the dentist.
If left untreated,
dental problems can snowball quickly.
The dentist?
Sir, here are the documents to sign
and the script.
The Women's Kingdom?
Oh right. The one with Shin Seo-ri?
Their marketing team proposed
product placement.
But TV shows barely offer
worthwhile ad exposure anymore.
I said we'd pass. You can just skip it.
"Consummation"?
CONSUMMATION ON A RAINY NIGHT
Come now, stay still.
I am embarrassed.
-Come now, come here…
-Your Majesty.
Why are you in such a hurry?
What is there to be so shy about?
One would think you
a blushing bride on her wedding night.
-Come here.
-Your Majesty.
Please put out the lights first.
Right.
I will not put out the lights tonight.
I wish to see
every part of you in full light.
Your Majesty!
This is bull…
I'm sorry!
I was feeling sleepy, so I took a sip.
-Damn it. I'm so pissed off!
-So sorry I had the coffee.
Mr. Son,
get in touch with whoever is
in charge of product placement right now.
Come on, Assistant Director.
You can't just cut a whole scene
without even a heads-up.
What are we supposed to do?
It was an urgent request
from one of our partners.
And the substantial amount
led him to make accommodations.
No accommodations were made for us.
That's just colluding behind closed doors.
Have her memorize the new script.
This was totally avoidable
with proper writing from the start.
Why are you here,
barking orders to memorize it?
What was it replaced with?
The Sericulture Rite scene.
What? The Sericulture Rite?
Seri? Siri? Sherry?
THE WOMEN'S KINGDOM 2
BIOJEI REVISED SCRIPT
Lunacy has struck the Inner Court.
This rite is the Queen's authority alone.
Who is she to step in?
What can we do?
The Queen is indisposed with indigestion.
It is not like we can postpone it.
Oh my. Look at that. A butterfly.
I kept catching a lovely scent.
It must have been Lady Jang's scent.
Even her skin is as flawless
as white jade.
They say she who commands
the finest complexion
commands the palace.
By the time the stormy seas settle
Into stillness,
On such a day, shall I expect you to come
from beyond that hill yonder?
Jeweled sunlight on a memorial day
is beautiful.
Even more beautiful still…
Is the luminous texture of your skin.
Biojei.
Cut! That was great.
So good.
Great work, everyone. Good job.
-Oh, dear.
-My shoulder.
Have the writer
and director both gone crazy?
Who sends a revision notice on the day of?
Well, that product placement deal
that just came in was massive.
You know historical dramas
are always tight on budget.
If this can cover the deficit, we should--
Yeah, but why did they have
to replace my solo scene to do that?
It's so annoying.
Then you should've volunteered
for the product placement from the start.
I'm not insane.
Why would I shoot an ad for free?
For Shin Seo-ri's company?
You know, you always snap whenever
Shin Seo-ri is mentioned.
Could that be an inferiority complex?
Why the hell would I feel
that way about her?
Damn it.
Cut!
Okay!
Seo-ri, that was great.
I heard she's an acting prodigy.
She has such good diction.
Our director hit the jackpot.
She's really something else.
Why would I ever…
Even on break, make sure you eat properly.
You're on the smaller side for your age,
so eating well matters.
Hey, Dad.
Can I come for a visit?
I've been telling the nanny
for a while now
that I want to visit you.
Seo-jun, you know how busy I am.
Even if you come to Korea,
I don't have time to play.
Seo-jun.
Please book me a ticket
to the US for this weekend.
For an early Friday morning flight.
Yeah.
Sir, we just got a call from the hospital.
How could they lose a patient?
An unconscious one, no less.
She was definitely unconscious
during the rounds.
What about CCTV?
No idea where she went?
She took a taxi from the main gate.
We're tracking her likely whereabouts now.
Find her location as quickly as possible.
She must be kept
from making any outside contact.
Especially the Chairman or Se-gye.
Look at Shin Seo-ri's quick thinking.
Your acrostic improv earlier was amazing.
I had to do it either way.
They were even getting
a butterfly to land.
No point in holding back.
-Want one?
-Hard candy?
A sweet reward after hard work.
Seo-ri!
-Amazing.
-Director.
That last take was really great.
Actors absolutely loathe shooting
product placement these days.
Since they all loathe it so,
I suppose a nobody like me
has no choice but to step up.
No, not at all.
That's a misunderstanding.
The CEO of our partner company
asked for you specifically. Come on now.
The CEO himself?
That's what I'm telling you.
The CEO himself. Amazing.
If you want something done,
do it yourself.
The bedroom scene
was definitely cut, right?
Hey, you there.
Hold on a second.
-Who are you?
-Me?
I'm a major investor in this drama.
I had a question for you.
Your bedroom scene
with Shin Seo-ri was cut, right?
Mister, you can't just wander in here.
Are you a stalker fan or what?
Hey, Manager!
There will never be
any bedroom scenes in the future.
So avoid any unnecessary physical contact.
Right, so who are you?
Me?
Her stalker fan.
Right.
Yeah.
You cannot keep barging in
unannounced like this.
Are you trying to be a hoodlum?
No, it's nothing like that.
I've been stressing over
every little thing,
to the extent I'm having stress dreams.
It's time to start living as I please.
Are you not doing that already?
Changing people's scripts…
That script saw a few edits,
thanks to me, right?
A few?
From what I heard, the male lead
has a terrible reputation.
He ruins kiss scenes on purpose
and bugs his co-stars privately
to run lines off-set.
He's the biggest creep ever.
I was just protecting my actor…
Wait, why am I
making excuses right now?
If anything, you should be thanking me.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thanks to you, I totally stole that scene.
Just with words?
Here, eat this.
I absolutely hate sweets.
-Don't eat it then.
-Come on now.
Sickeningly sweet.
Look at this drool. Gross.
Let's create
a position for Se-gye in the company.
We can't keep him
out there forever, can we?
You should ask Se-gye what he thinks, too.
A startup that size
alongside a role here will be hard.
He can leave Biojei to a professional CEO.
He can do anything
if he sets his mind to it.
Is there anywhere
you want to go with me?
Anywhere I want to go?
We've never been on a proper date before.
Let's see.
A good place to go at this hour…
Degeneracy comes so naturally to you.
What is with that look?
No, my tooth actually hurts.
You should have let the sweet
melt in your mouth.
Chomping like that?
Your teeth don't stand a chance.
Melt it? So tedious.
You should savor the good things.
The rich don't know how
to cherish and savor anything.
That's not true.
I cherish you a lot.
I don't chew you up all at once.
Wait. Blood! There is blood!
Blood? What blood?
Well…
His complexion is fine. It is not poison.
Since he is bleeding and in pain,
I suspect it is a tooth of wisdom.
The Dongui Bogam prescribes
a mixture of calcined chicken droppings
and straw shoes, along with deer musk.
Droppings and straw shoes?
What are you dawdling for?
Your patient is in agony.
At least administer some acupuncture!
-I'm not in that much pain.
-Stop.
What does the patient know? Stay still.
Calm down, Shin Seo-ri.
It's an impacted wisdom tooth.
You're going to need surgery.
-"Impacted"?
-Just pull it out.
What sort of wisdom tooth
requires surgery?
It depends on the case.
The impacted wisdom tooth on the left
will need to be surgically removed.
So, shall we proceed
with the surgery immediately?
Yes, whatever it takes.
Hurry up and do it. Come on.
-Just a moment.
-This is why I hate the dentist.
Open your mouth. Open.
OPERATING ROOM
Never in my life did I think
I'd be put under for a wisdom tooth.
Good thing we came to a large clinic.
-I saved your precious life again.
-No.
A wisdom tooth isn't
exactly life-threatening.
No time like the present.
Just get it properly treated now.
And let it melt next time.
What? Are you leaving?
It is late. I should get going.
Exactly, it's late.
Just stay.
The post-surgery pain alone…
You said it was not fatal.
Still, I'm getting surgery here.
Don't you think abandoning
someone you're seeing is a little rude?
What a novel way of asking me to stay
and wait on you hand and foot.
Let's head in now.
I'm counting on you.
You'd better not leave.
Promise me.
Administering the anesthesia now.
O Heaven.
I want to know you and be known by you.
It shall never fade
as long as life endures.
Until the mountains have no peaks,
and the river waters run dry.
Until the thunder rolls in winter
and the snow falls in the summer.
Until heaven and earth become one.
Only then would I dare to part from you.
This…
I cannot bring myself to deliver.
Sir, are you awake?
Where did she go?
You may experience a sore throat
and a nosebleed from the intubation.
For 48 hours following the extraction,
cold compresses are recommended.
If everything looks good
tomorrow morning, you'll be discharged.
Excuse me.
Did she leave?
Who?
She left.
That heartless woman.
Is that Byeokjo wood?
The lightning-struck jujube tree.
When I was little,
my dad was a peddler.
Sometimes women asked him to get it
to pray for their sick sons.
Who are you praying for?
Your father? Your brother?
Wait, you said you had no family.
Seriously?
I thought you left.
You told me not to go.
I went to get some ice.
Hold on.
Your hands are frozen.
You shouldn't have carried that
with your bare hands.
How else would I carry it? On my head?
You said you are hurting.
I had to do something.
This is all I can do for you.
Still, it's too cold.
Stop that!
Patients should just lie still.
That is how you help.
You look just like a pufferfish.
With those puffy cheeks.
You should just go home.
You're enjoying this way too much.
I feel like I keep losing face
ever since we started seeing each other.
About that dream you had…
Have you had any more?
Why?
You said it was nonsense,
but you were clearly bothered by it.
The resemblance must be strong
if it confused you that much.
I began to grow a bit curious.
Well, the dream
is a bit dark.
I anticipate a sad ending.
-"Sad"?
-Yeah, it's about being framed
and locked up. That sort of thing.
Isn't a sad ending inevitable?
I think exile is coming soon too.
Exile…
Then who are you in all this?
Me?
They call me "Your Highness"
or something like that.
"His Highness, the Grand Prince."
I must be a prince
or something like that.
No surprise there.
I should have known
a bad gut feeling is never wrong.
It seemed like that man
felt a certain way about that woman,
the court lady named Kang Dan-sim.
Resentment.
Love…
He felt
a deep yearning for her.
"O Heaven."
"I wish to live forever in your embrace."
"Until the mountains erode
and the rivers run dry."
"Until thunder strikes in winter
and heavy snow falls in summer."
"Until the day heaven
and earth become one."
"Only then shall I part with you."
A whole lot of sentiment.
He was in love with that woman.
Like a fool.
SUCCESSION IN FULL SWING WITH MOCHANG
What's with that dress?
It'll only make you look short.
I told you that you always need
a higher waistline because you're short.
You run a business,
yet you still have no sense of style.
It's been a while, Mom.
Still as beautiful
and foul-mouthed as ever.
Is that any way to speak to your mother?
You got back ages ago
but never once came home.
Chasing after him
when you're not even married yet.
I guess I find it more comfortable there.
No one to breathe
down my neck every second.
What?
This actually works out.
I wanted to speed things up anyway.
Invite us over.
Se-gye and me.
MOCHANG HEIR
ATTENDS CHA'S BRAND LAUNCH
Look at them
telling the whole world about it.
Ms. Shin,
we should get together soon.
Is it him?
GRANDMA
You don't even have money.
This is way too expensive.
Tell them to change my room right now.
Why would you want
to be packed in like sardines again?
So you can fight?
Fight? Don't be ridiculous.
Those old ladies were just bored
and running their mouths for nothing.
You said you wanted to be discharged soon.
You will recover faster there.
Is it not sunnier there?
Even the air feels different, no?
Not really.
And I have money!
Did you forget I am on TV?
I am making loads of it,
so do not worry about that.
Just eat well
and focus on getting better.
Look at this old lady
living in luxury
thanks to her sweet grandchild.
But Seo-ri,
I like being around people.
Rather than be all alone by yourself,
you should have a little bustle around you
to remind you that you're alive.
No matter how great you are,
no one can live completely alone.
Sure, people thrive on feeling superior,
but that's no way to live.
You'll just end up withering away alone.
Hey, remember that young lady
I shared a table with the other day?
Is she a regular?
She is. She's here
two or three times a week.
Why do you ask?
Well, she just left quite an impression.
A young person eating alone like that…
She must have no friends.
Many kids come alone now.
Right.
She has
no friends?
I see.
What do you think of her?
How's her character?
And what's it to you?
Looking for a new wife?
You crazy old hag.
Have you officially gone senile?
Her character is a lost cause.
It's like half her tongue is missing,
dropping all her honorifics
left and right.
I see.
Is that so?
No matter how great you are,
no one can live completely alone.
Kang Dan-sim.
Never set foot in this place again.
Sure, people thrive on feeling superior,
but that's no way to live.
You'll just end up withering away alone.
They call me "Your Highness"
or something like that.
"His Highness, the Grand Prince."
You're finally home.
Did you eat?
Enjoy.
So, how are your teeth?
Are you all better now?
Of course.
It was just a wisdom tooth. No big deal.
But you bled so much.
Have yourself some herbal medicine made.
It can only do you good.
Well, you know,
I tend not to rely on stuff like that.
More importantly,
I said let's get a meal. What is this?
We're out on some chaotic street.
I think the bustle is nice.
What if someone recognizes you?
Honestly,
sometimes you just totally forget
you're a celebrity.
And you shouldn't stay out too late.
The streets are dark.
What am I? A kid?
Watching over me…
Why wouldn't I?
We're seeing each other.
Don't I deserve to worry about you?
As if seeing each other is a big deal.
You sure do expect a lot for a trial run.
I'll personally handle Grandfather,
so stop worrying.
And the arranged marriage…
I'll sort all of that out soon enough,
so don't stress.
You want to end it already?
Why not milk it a bit longer?
-What?
-Since you already started,
milk it for all it is worth.
The papers are already saying
how good this is for you.
Why not go all out while you are at it?
No need to tiptoe around me.
I never tiptoed.
I've never once tiptoed
around anyone, ever.
You sure tiptoed like a ballerina
around your grandfather.
It's all talk with you.
I just…
wanted to make you look good.
What?
I did that
so you'd make a good impression on him.
Your grandfather
seemed quite fond of that little schemer.
Then again, she did seem
to have pretty solid backing.
"Little Schemer"?
You gave her a nickname already?
I can't deny that.
But don't worry.
"Backing"?
I don't need any of that.
You know how exceptional I am.
Look at me.
I'm doing great all by myself already.
"Cream rises to the top."
The nail that sticks out
gets hammered down.
If you stand out too much,
you will just wither away all alone.
I have seen it time and time again.
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
Listen.
You need to watch out for Choi Mun-do.
And do not trust anyone.
I can take care of myself.
I told you not to worry.
Do you…
Do you think the world is that easy?
Anyone could be lining up to attack you,
but you're focusing on
taking me out on dates.
Indulging in petty love games?
Yeah, I find the world easy.
It will always be spiraling
into insanity.
Why overcomplicate things?
Regardless of what you think,
if you have no regrets,
you have nothing to lose in this world.
But…
it's you I find difficult.
It's weird.
It gets harder as time goes on.
Maybe it's because I like you so much?
Stop it.
It is pathetic.
So what if I'm a little pathetic?
Then stop showing up in my dreams.
What if…
-it were not a dream?
-What?
What if it were not a dream?
What would you do then?
What are you talking about?
The court lady with no family or friends.
The naive girl, cluelessly suffering
through initiation rites.
If I were
that woman, Kang Dan-sim…
what would you do?
If I were that ruthless woman,
solely focused on surviving…
You…
COURT LADY KANG DAN-SIM
NO SEARCH RESULTS
What am I even doing?
MS. SHIN, WE SHOULD GET TOGETHER SOON
It seemed like that man
felt a certain way about that woman,
the court lady named Kang Dan-sim.
Love…
He felt…
a deep yearning for her.
He was in love with that woman.
Like a fool.
I can never truly know if he had
such affections for me.
And even if he did,
what good would it do me now?
TIME TRAVEL TO THE JOSEON DYNASTY
THE GRAND HISTORY: 1392 TO 2026
SEOUL MUSEUM OF HISTORY
Why do you stare at it so intently?
Does a plum blossom flowering
in midsummer unsettle you so?
Back when I painted this,
I had buried him in my heart.
Hold on!
You're that woman from last time, right?
Royal Consort Kang!
Hello.
I'm writing my thesis on reinterpreting
that infamous villainess, you see.
That's why I was so excited
to hear you speak.
Wow.
I guess you're still on that quest.
The story of Royal Consort Kang.
If I were that woman, Kang Dan-sim,
what would you do?
Sir.
I thought you were ready to go,
but you seem lost in your thoughts.
Mr. Son, do you believe in past lives?
Past lives, all of a sudden?
Well, I guess I do.
My family's been Buddhist for generations.
So past lives, reincarnation…
That all makes sense to you?
I don't see why not.
This life is our present life.
In between our past and next lives.
That's the gist of it.
But why the sudden interest?
Well, the thing is…
Hypothetically speaking,
if someone said they came from the past,
what would that mean?
When in the past?
It's ridiculous.
-Joseon.
-Joseon?
Did someone from "Joseon"
tell you that your ancestors are angry?
Did they ask for memorial service money?
That's a classic cult recruitment line.
No, it's not like that.
Tell them you have no need
for such ancestors.
No memorial service.
True ancestors bless. Evil spirits harm.
Please come out now.
Damn it, I should never have told her
about the dream.
Now there's a weird wall between us.
You're an actor, right?
The Women's Kingdom 2?
Wow.
No wonder you had such a unique vibe.
You know, after I started interning here,
I discovered something really amazing.
The piece itself isn't fully intact,
so it's not popular with visitors,
but we refer to it as
The Portrait of a Beauty.
Come take a look.
She looks like you, doesn't she?
It's only half a painting,
but no matter how I look at it,
it looks just like you.
I guess doppelgängers really do exist.
But what's even crazier is
that this is actually a love letter.
If you look on the right, there's a poem.
O Heaven.
And it's not just any paper.
It's drawn on precious mulberry paper.
Seeing as they painted this
and even wrote a love letter,
this was no ordinary crush.
It's like the ultimate unspoken love.
Isn't it so romantic?
A gift for my dearest companion.
-It is the Grand Prince.
-Hey, make way!
He is not just any royal.
He is a full brother to the Crown Prince.
Gosh, he is quite a looker.
Is he not?
I heard he is quite the womanizer.
Just look at that pretty-boy face.
And what happens after you follow him?
Will you two run away together?
Right, keep your mouth shut.
Bury your feelings deep in your heart.
That is the only way to survive.
Take it.
This is from me, not the Grand Prince.
May this serve as the token
of your lone survival.
But still…
How could you even call that love?
If it remains unspoken
and you ache in silence…
as if your heart was being crushed
by some great boulder…
that is not love.
Love, my foot.
Unable to share
even a fraction of my feelings…
I just rubbed some pebbles like an idiot
and clenched my fists.
Do you truly harbor affection for me?
I do.
Screw this damn world,
and let your heart flutter with me.
Let me be your only one too.
That ends now.
No more acting like a fool.
I am done with that.
GEONGUK APOTHECARY
Excuse me, shopkeeper.
Give me some medicinal herbs.
Prepare the most precious
and expensive ones quickly.
So?
Do you have a spot for Se-gye?
Yes, well…
Creating a position is easy,
but I'm worried about internal backlash.
It'd be better for Se-gye
if he were welcomed back by all.
It would look better too.
Do you have a plan in mind?
There is a position that remains unfilled.
Why don't you let him handle
the US branch?
If he proves his ability
and contributes to the company,
the opposition will quickly die down.
I see.
I'll think about it.
Why is this so watery?
-What?
-It is completely watery.
There are no herbs at all.
It is just full of plain water.
Not plain water. A decoction.
You must be talking about packaged herbs.
Our clinic doesn't dispense
packaged herbs.
It'd also be hard for you
to brew this yourself.
So you mean
it has all been brewed already?
Goodness me.
Just the thought of squatting
to brew each packet
had my knees aching.
The world really has gotten better.
Thanks.
Cha Se-gye, come here
as soon as you are done with work.
I need to tell you something.
CHA SE-GYE: OKAY
Why hide my feelings?
No sense in letting them go to waste.
Yes.
My schedule changed.
I can't make it this weekend.
Don't tell Seo-jun I'm coming just yet.
I'll see how it goes and call you back.
AIDE SEO
Sir, an announcement
has been posted on the intranet.
PERSONNEL APPOINTMENT NOTICE
US BRANCH MANAGER
CHOI MUN-DO
CHAIL GROUP CHAIRMAN CHA DAL-SU
Sir, we got a call
from that hospitalized nurse.
She said she had something to tell you.
I might be a bit late,
but I will be there eventually.
What brings you here this late?
Did you join a cult?
I'm off.
CHOI MUN-DO, CHAIL E&C
I've been thinking about it too.
How desperate one must be
for the chairman's seat
to resort to such pathetic stalking.
Still,
you shouldn't have broken the law.
I'm so sorry.
Even if I was blinded by the money,
I should've never done as I was told.
I swear I will pay for what I've done.
Just please spare my life.
So?
Do you actually believe
you have leverage over me?
I get that you're willing
to throw away your pride
and risk your own life for this,
but what about Seo-jun?
Sure.
Like you said,
I made extreme sacrifices to get here.
And what about you?
What exactly have you done?
All you ever did was mess up
and abuse your power.
Do you think you're qualified?
Forget it.
Let's just stop here.
What are you doing?
I have something to show you too.
What is this?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
When a man and a woman
get together in secret,
what do you think is going on?
Don't make me laugh.
What would someone like you do
with a woman like her?
You obviously brought these,
thinking you could somehow test me.
You have a lot of faith in her.
Who knows what kind of deal was made?
You seem to be
under some grave misconception.
Too bad.
As if I'd ever get involved
with someone like her.
Maybe it could work on Uncle?
"Someone like her"?
That old man is still heartbroken
over his one and only precious son,
who threw his life away
for the wrong woman.
I wonder
how he'll view Shin Seo-ri.
You know better than anyone
what Uncle did to your mom.
You must be insane.
Yeah.
That's what vulnerability gets you.
People naturally grow weaker
the more they have to lose.
Give up on returning to the company,
and I won't interfere.
And of course,
Uncle will never need to know any of this.
Damn it.
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
What is this?
He said he would be late.
Jeez.
Cha Se-gye.
You said you would be late.
It's late. Where were you?
Yeah, I had to take care of something.
I've had a headache all day
because of the bomb you dropped.
And yet you look completely fine.
How draining for me.
Cha Se-gye, about that--
After I listened to your nonsense,
I was made a fool of.
Yet here I am anyway.
I somehow crawled back here.
No.
I just--
Do you really have
that little faith in me?
I hoped we wouldn't have any secrets.
I heard you met Choi Mun-do.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-Well, that is--
I heard he offered you some sort of deal.
You should have told me.
Whatever it is, I can do more for you.
I thought I gave you
enough reason to trust me…
but I guess I didn't.
How much more do I have to do?
How much longer
must I cling to you and grovel
for you to open up?
If you don't feel the same way,
I'd rather you just use me openly.
I'm more than willing to let you use me.
Yeah.
This is the Shin Seo-ri I know.
If you really are that ruthless
as you claim,
don't half-heartedly pretend
to be a decent person.
Stop worrying about me.
Just think about yourself
if you're going to play the villain!
Then commit to it.
Let go.
Let go!
Let go of me! Let go!
I can't…
think straight for even a moment
thanks to you.
Whoever you are…
wherever you came from…
I believe it all.
What?
Yeah. I believe whatever you say…
so just keep your eyes on me.
Forget all those other bastards
and just look at me.
Please.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
We're done testing the waters?
-Let us go on a date, Cha Se-gye.
-All of a sudden?
I am going to be beyond generous.
You're my Seo-ri's boyfriend?
Please forgive me.
We're looking at a leadership change.
The young master just arrived
at the head office.
Do you honestly think
I'll just step down quietly?
-Have you seen the patient in Room 12?
-You sure you can handle that?
Luring and threatening
a helpless old woman?
You have nothing to lose, Ms. Shin.
I hate seeing you involved
with Choi Mun-do. I hate it!
You are even worse than him.
You are even more hurtful!
I want Se-gye to end up
with someone who has love to spare.
Shin Seo-ri, just pick up your phone.
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim